(rock music)
(cheering)
- Your turn, come on!
You better know this (censored)!
♪ Well, we got no choice ♪
♪ All the girls and boys ♪
♪ Making all that noise ♪
♪ 'Cause they found new toys ♪
♪ Well, we can't salute ya ♪
♪ Can't find a flag ♪
♪ If that don't suit ya ♪
♪ That's a drag ♪
♪ School's out for summer ♪
I can't hear you!
♪ School's out forever ♪
♪ School's been blown to pieces ♪
♪ No more pencils ♪
♪ No more books ♪
♪ No more teacher's dirty looks, yeah ♪
♪ Well, we got no class ♪
♪ And we got no principals ♪
♪ And we got no intelligence ♪
♪ We can't even think
of a word that rhymes ♪
♪ School's out for summer ♪
♪ School's out forever ♪
♪ School's been blown to pieces ♪
♪ No more pencils ♪
♪ No more books ♪
♪ No more teacher's dirty looks ♪
♪ Out for summer ♪
♪ Out 'til fall ♪
♪ We might not come back at all ♪
♪ School's out for summer ♪
Come on (indistinct)!
♪ School's out forever ♪
♪ School's been blown to pieces ♪
♪ My school's out completely ♪
Thank you, Birmingham!
(applauding and cheering)